Kheel Center AV Collection 6118 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center AV Collection
1943-2009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
6118 AV
56.44 cubic feet
51.8 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials, phonograph records, videocassettes, audiocassettes, motion pictures (visual works).
This is a collection of phonograph discs, VHS video cassettes, audio cassettes, CD-ROMs and motion picture films among other forms of media.
7735225
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 19, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Working class; Working class -- Songs and music; Working class in motion pictures; Addams, Jane, 1860-1935; Belafonte, Harry, 1927-; Davis, Ossie; Dee, Ruby; Glazer, Joe; Glazer, Tom; Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924; Guthrie, Woody, 1912-1967; Johnson, Lyndon B.(Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973; Juravich, Tom; Kennedy, John F.; Penn, Larry; Seeger, Pete, 1919-; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; American Management Association; Bread and Roses Cultural Project; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; International Association of Machinists; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; United Farm Workers; United Hatters, Cap, and Millinery Workers International Union; United Steelworkers of America; Utility Workers Union of America
7735225
- Song of Guaranteed Wage and I Like Ike by J. Glazer, 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  #54 -- 12" album
- A Century of Song, 2 (Box 1)
  #68 -- 12" album
- Songs of Coal by J. Glazer, 3 (Box 1)
  #73 -- 12" album
- Golden Spike centennial by C. Sandburg, 4 (Box 1)
  #76 -- 12" album
- Coal Tattoo, 5 (Box 1)
  #77 -- 7" lp (45rpm) - 3 copies
- American Industrial Ballads by P. Seeger, 6 (Box 1)
  #79 -- 12" album
- Movin On, UTA, 7 (Box 1)
  #80 -- 12" album
- I Hate the Capitalist System, 8 (Box 1)
  #81 - 12" album
- Huela Records - United Farm Workers, 9 (Box 1)
  #82 -- 12" album
- Movin On, 10 (Box 1)
  #91 - 12" album
- The Human Condition by Beverly Grant, 11 (Box 1)
  #99 -- 12 " album
- Steady As She Goes; Songs and Chanties from the days of Commercial Sail: Louis Killen; Jeff Warner; Gerret Warner; Fud Benson, 12 (Box 1)
  #106 - 12" album
- Songs of the Wobblies / Joe Glazer, 13 (Box 1)
  #107 -- 12" album
- Songs of Steel & Struggle / Sung by Joe Glazer with the Charlie Byrd Trio, 14 (Box 1)
  #108 -- 12" album
- Songs for Woodworkers / Joe Glazer Sings; Forty Years of Progress 1937-1977; International Woodworkers of America, 15 (Box 1)
  #105 -- 12" album
- Groundwork: Songs of Working People / Joe Uehlein, 16 (Box 1)
  #117 -- 12" album
- Workin' For a Livin' / Songs by Larry Penn: Collector Records 1931, 17 (Box 1)
  #118 + #111 -- 12" album (3 copies)
- Gallant Lads Are We: Songs of the British Industrial Revolution / sung by Louis Killen, 18 (Box 1)
  #119 -- 12" album
- Tipple Loom & Rail, 19 (Box 1)
  #120 -- 12" album
- Trade Unionist, Socialist, Revolutionary 1855-1926 - Eugene V. Debs: An Historical Narrative written and produced by Bernard Sanders, 20 (Box 1)
  #110 -- 12" album
- Bread and Raises: Songs for Working Women / sung by Bobbie McGee, 21 (Box 1)
  #126 -- 12" album
- Image of History: Twenty Years of the C.I.O., 22 (Box 1)
  #127 -- 12" album
- Solidarity Day, 23 (Box 1)
  #128 -- 12" album
- Jellybean Blues: Songs of Reaganomics / Sung by Joe Glazer, 24 (Box 1)
  #129 -- 12" album
- Rising Again: Union Songs for the '80s / Tom Juravich, 25 (Box 1)
  #130 - 12" album
- Ossie & Ruby and Bread and Roses / Ossie Davis, Ruby Dee: an 1199 Bread and Roses Recording, 26 (Box 1)
  #138 -- 12" album
- Jellybean Blues / Sung by Joe Glazer: Volume two, 27 (Box 1)
  #136 -- 12" album
- This Land is Your Land: Songs of Social Justice, 28 (Box 1)
  #121 -- 12" album
- 8 New Songs For Labor / sung by Joe Glazer and the Elm City Four, 29 (Box 1)
  #123 -- 12" album -- 2 copies
- Songs of the FDR Years / Roy Berkeley with Tim Woodbridge, 30 (Box 1)
  Folk and Country Songs of the FDR Years -- #124 -- 12" album
- Take Care: a Musical Revue of Life in the Hospitals / District 1199's Bread & Roses Project presents, 31 (Box 1)
  #137 -- 12" album -- 4 copies
- Pete Seeger: Archive of Folk Music, 32 (Box 1)
  #139 -- 12" album
- Work's Many Voices - volume I, 33 (Box 1)
  #141 -- 12" album
- Work's Many Voices, Volume II, 34 (Box 1)
  #142 -- 12" album
- CIO - Union Label, 1 (Box 2)
  #259 -- 12" album
- The Inheritance / narrated by Robert Ryan, 2 (Box 2)
  #308 -- 12" album -- 6 copies
- CIO Favorite American Union Songs / sung by Tom Glazer, 3 (Box 2)
  #260 -- 12 " album -- 3 record set
- The Union Democracy Built, 4 (Box 2)
  #309 -- 12" album -- 2 copies
- Carry On / Pete Seeger, Jane Sapp, Si Kahn: Songs of American Working People, 5 (Box 2)
  #143 -- 12" album
- Step 'n Blue / Bucky Halker, 6 (Box 2)
  #145 -- 12" album
- Joe Glazer: Singing BRAC, 7 (Box 2)
  #147 -- 12" album
- Two/Two for the Union, 8 (Box 2)
  #148 -- 12" album
- The Northeast Sings, 9 (Box 2)
  #149 -- 12" album -- 2 copies
- Work's Many Voices: Volume I, II, 10 (Box 2)
  #150 -- 12" album -- 2 record set
- Sacco & Vanzetti: Ballads of Sacco & Vanzetti / sung by Woody Guthrie, 11 (Box 2)
  #174 -- 12" album
- A Supervisor's Day / Eugene E. Epstein, 12 (Box 2)
  #159 -- 12" album -- 2 record set
- Go To Arbitration! / Irving A. Delloff, William J. Jaffe, 13 (Box 2)
  #158 -- 12" album
- Working in I.L.R., 14 (Box 2)
  #163 -- 12" album
- I Can Hear It Now vol. 1-3 / by Edward R. Murrow and Fred W. Friendly, 15 (Box 2)
  #165 -- 12" album -- 3 record set
- Mark Twain and other folk favorites / Harry Belafonte, 16 (Box 2)
  #167 -- 12" album
- The People Act: a tape recorded radio series, 17 (Box 2)
  #170 -- 12" album
- The Rainbow Quest: Pete Seeger, 18 (Box 2)
  #173 -- 12" album
- The Central Pension Fund Presents Joe Glazer Live at Vail, 19 (Box 2)
  #175 -- 12" album
- The Brothers Isley, 20 (Box 2)
  #176 -- 12" album
- RLEA - Working on the Railroads, 1 (Box 3)
  #1 -- 12" album -- 6 copies -- 1 Dubbed copy
- March on Washington, 2 (Box 3)
  #2 -- 12" album
- Talking Union / with the Almanac Singers, 3 (Box 3)
  #3 -- 12" album
- The Original Talking Union / Pete Seeger & Chorus, 4 (Box 3)
  #4 -- 12" album
- Songs of the Coal Mines / by Merle Travis, 5 (Box 3)
  # 5 -- 12" album
- Songs of Joe Hill / by Joe Blazer, 6 (Box 3)
  # 6 -- 12" album
- 900 Miles & other R.R. songs, 7 (Box 3)
  #7 -- 12" album
- Textile Voices / by Joe Grazer, 8 (Box 3)
  #8 -- 12" album
- The Songs & Stories of Aunt Molly Jackson, 9 (Box 3)
  #10 -- 12" album
- Picket Line Songs, 10 (Box 3)
  #11 -- 12" album -- 2 copies
- Songs for a Better Tomorrow, 11 (Box 3)
  #12 -- 12" album
- March on Washington, 12 (Box 3)
  #13 -- 12" album
- A. Vanderbilt - Do's & Don't's, 13 (Box 3)
  #14 -- 12" album
- British Industrial Folk Songs, 14 (Box 3)
  #15 -- 12" album
- Down in a Coal Mine / J. Glazer, 15 (Box 3)
  #16 -- 12" album
- Joe Glazer - Garbage, 16 (Box 3)
  #17 -- 12" album
- Martin Luther King Jr. at 1199, 17 (Box 3)
  #19 -- 12" album
- Back Home / by Merle Travis, 18 (Box 3)
  # 20 -- 12" album
- Sing a Labor Song, 19 (Box 3)
  #21 -- 10" album -- 2 records
- Portrait of Sam Gompers; Portrait of Jane Addams, 20 (Box 3)
  #22 -- 12" album
- The Magic Black Jack, UAW-CIO, 21 (Box 3)
  #23 -- 12" album -- 2 record set
- The Magic Black Jack: UAW-CIO #23, 22 (Box 3)
- The Magic Black Jack - UAW-CIO (pts. 3-4) #23, 23 (Box 3)
- Highlights, Second Constitutional Convention, AFL-CIO: December 1957 - Atlantic City, N.J. (collection 5974 AV), 24 (Box 3)
  This belongs to collection 5974 AV, and is being housed here.
- Give Away Boys and J. McCarthy's Bind / Joe Glazer, 1 (Box 4)
  #32 -- 10" album
- My Name is Mary Brown, 2 (Box 4)
  #34 -- 10" album -- 2 records
- A Promise and You Gotta Go Down / by J. Glazer, 3 (Box 4)
  #35 -- 10" album
- Solidarity and Give Away Boys / by J. Glazer, 4 (Box 4)
  #36 -- 10" album -- 2 records
- Solidarity Forever and Song of the Furniture Workers / by J. Glazer, 5 (Box 4)
  #44
- Image of Freedom and 20 Years of the CIO, 6 (Box 4)
  #26 -- 12" album
- New Songs of Labor / by Joe Glazer, 7 (Box 4)
  #27 -- 12" album -- 2 copies
- Discussion of Union Shop Amendment to RLA, 8 (Box 4)
  #28 -- 10" album
- Discussion of Railway Labor's Political League / Bros. of Railway Clerks, 9 (Box 4)
  #29 -- 10" album
- Excerpts from J.C. Petrillo's Testimony 1/21/1948, 10 (Box 4)
  #30 -- 12" album -- 3 parts -- 3 records
- 50th Anniv. Celebration Address / G. Harrison - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks, 11 (Box 4)
  #31 -- 12" album -- Damaged; unrecordable
- Midnight Vision / UAW-CIO Edu. Dept., 12 (Box 4)
  #39 -- 10" album -- damaged
- The Story of Henderson / Textile Worker's., 13 (Box 4)
  #41 -- 12" album
- Your Co.'s Record for 1948, 14 (Box 4)
  #42 -- 12" album -- 2 records
- Union Shop: the Moral Issue, 15 (Box 4)
  #45 -- 12" album
- Highlights - 2nd Const. Convention AFL-CIO 1957, 16 (Box 4)
  #46 -- 10" album
- The Railroad Worker and His Songs, 17 (Box 4)
  #47 -- 10" album -- 2 records
- A Message for You / Gen. Telephone Company of Michigan, 18 (Box 4)
  # 48 -- 33-1/3 rpm
- The Facts Behind the Figures / Union Oil of California, 19 (Box 4)
  # 49 -- 12" album
- Union Train / J. Glazer, 20 (Box 4)
  #51 -- 12" album
- 1958 Vote Spots, 21 (Box 4)
  #53 -- 12" album
- Taft-Hartley Act, 22 (Box 4)
  #70 -- 12" album
- Italy, Great Britain, France, Greece, Denmark, Austria, Holland, 23 (Box 4)
  #71 -- 10" albums -- 3 records
- Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs, 24 (Box 4)
  #98 -- 12" album
- Independent Sadie/Tom, Dick and Harry, 25 (Box 4)
  #162 -- 12" album
- Tessie Teller/Dewey Jones, 26 (Box 4)
  #162 -- 12" albums
- Harry Carey/George Gray, 27 (Box 4)
- Portrait of Samuel Gompers - A.F. of L.; Madge Smegoff Interviews, Lucy Robbins, 28 (Box 4)
  #294 -- 12" albums
- Slave Labor Camp Songs of the U.S.S.R., 29 (Box 4)
  #295 -- 12" album
- The Right to Strike, 1 (Box 5)
  #153 -- 12" album
- The Case of harassed Harry, 2 (Box 5)
  #154 -- 12" album
- Brain Beats Brawn, 3 (Box 5)
  #155 -- 12" album
- Cause and Cure, 4 (Box 5)
- Doctor's Orders, 5 (Box 5)
- Follow the Leader, 6 (Box 5)
- Guard Duty, 7 (Box 5)
  #155 -- 12" albums
- Production with Safety, 8 (Box 5)
- Right Dress, 9 (Box 5)
- Safety is in Order, 10 (Box 5)
- Stop, Look, and Listen, 11 (Box 5)
- Straight Talk from Foremen / George L. Germain, Denny L. Howell, 12 (Box 5)
  #156 -- 12" album
- Arbitration A La Mode (parts 1&2), 13 (Box 5)
  #157 -- 12" album
- Arbitration A La Mode (parts 3&4), 14 (Box 5)
- Supervisory Problems in the Plan / by McGraw-Hill, 15 (Box 5)
  #161 -- 12" album -- 3 records
- Abbie Swartz, 16 (Box 5)
- Alice, Jane and Agnes, 17 (Box 5)
- Joe and Bob, 18 (Box 5)
- We Shall Not Be Moved / Hold the Fort, 19 (Box 5)
  #164 -- 12" album
- Isaac Hayes, 20 (Box 5)
  #168 -- 12" album
- Let's Live Democracy, 21 (Box 5)
  #177 - 12" album
- Chicago Report: Railroad Workers' Rally, 1 (Box 6)
  #310 -- 12" album
- Chicago Report: Railroad Workers' Rally, 2 (Box 6)
- Chicago Report: Railroad Workers' Rally, 3 (Box 6)
- Chicago Report: Railroad Workers' Rally, 4 (Box 6)
- Chicago Report: Railroad Workers' Rally, 5 (Box 6)
- Chicago Report: Railroad Workers' Rally, 6 (Box 6)
- No title, 7 (Box 6)
  no #-- 12" album
- Image of History 10 Years in the CIO, 8 (Box 6)
- Mr. Turner, Carbide and Carbon, Dec. 7, 1945, 9 (Box 6)
  #311 -- 12" album -- 2 records
- Working on the Railroads, 10 (Box 6)
  no # -- 12" album -- 24 copies
- We Work - We Sing! / New York Cloak Joint Board, 28th ILGWU Convention, Chicago, 1 (Box 7)
  #43 -- 10" album -- 2 copies
- There is no better way: Sam Church Jr., 2 (Box 7)
  #109 -- 7" LP
- Trying to Break My Union / by Tom Juravich, 1981; 3 (Box 7)
  #125 -- 7" LP
- Talking Union/the Almanac Singers; Dedicated to the memory of Joe Hill, 4 (Box 7)
  #122 -- 12" album -- 3 records
- Interview About Worker Performance, 5 (Box 7)
  #160 -- 10" LP
- Have a Heart Taft-Hartley, 6 (Box 7)
  #169 -- 10" LP
- A Progress Report, 7 (Box 7)
  #171 -- 10" LP
- Corporations Don't Have Hearts; Aug. 3, 1947, 8 (Box 7)
  #172 -- 10" LP
- Songs of the Wobblies / sung by Joe Glazer and Bill Friedland, 9 (Box 7)
  #178 -- 10" LP
- The Railroad Worker and His Songs, 10 (Box 7)
  #47 -- 10" LP -- 36 copies
- Highlights, Second Constitutional Convention, AFL-CIO - Dec. 1957-Atlantic City, N.J. (5974 AV), 11 (Box 7)
  one audio disc, being housed here, belongs to collection - 5974 AV
- It's the Woman Who Buys: Program 4 / produced for United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, 1 (Box 8)
  #24 -- 16" album
- Boomer Jones / presented by International Association of Machinists, 2 (Box 8)
  #25 -- 16" album -- 2 copies
- Ives-Taft Debate: Open Hearing Program -- 4/22/1947, 3 (Box 8)
  #33 -- 16" album -- 2 copies
- CIO - Wage Case, 4 (Box 8)
  #37 -- 16" album
- Jewel Tea Co. - Annual Report for 1946, 5 (Box 8)
  #38 -- 16" album
- Raise Wages - Not Prices / based on Robert Nathan's "A National Wage Policy for 1947", 6 (Box 8)
  #40 -- 16" album
- Understanding Industrial Relations, Series No. 1 - Program No. 4 - Developing Understanding of Industrial and Labor Relations, 7 (Box 8)
  #179 -- 16" album -- 2 records
- How to Buy Taft-Hartley, 8 (Box 8)
  #180 -- 16" album
- Public Power Story, 9 (Box 8)
  #181 -- 16" album
- Butch Your Union Button, 10 (Box 8)
  #182 -- 16" album
- Your Vote - A Priceless Heritage, 11 (Box 8)
  #183 -- 16" album
- Election Day is the Pay-Off, 12 (Box 8)
  #184 -- 16" album
- Preparing for the Future, 13 (Box 8)
  #185 -- 16" album
- New Men at Home, 14 (Box 8)
  #186 -- 16" album
- Mr. Fraud, the Right-to-Wreck Man, 15 (Box 8)
  #187 -- 16" album
- Communism - U.S. Brand, 16 (Box 8)
  #188 -- 16" album -- 3 copies
- Elmira Forum, 17 (Box 8)
  #189 -- 16" album
- Svenson's Seniority, 18 (Box 8)
  #190 -- 16" album
- Labor's Challenge, 19 (Box 8)
  #191 -- 16" album
- Labor's Challenge, 20 (Box 8)
  #192 -- 16" album
- Safety for Sale, 21 (Box 8)
  #193 -- 16" album
- Fair and Cool, 22 (Box 8)
  #194 -- 16" album
- Saga of 666, 23 (Box 8)
  #195 -- 16" album
- In Pursuit of Health, 24 (Box 8)
  #196 -- 16" album
- Hand Into Fist, 25 (Box 8)
  #197 -- 16" album
- Heart of the Union, 26 (Box 8)
  #198 -- 16" album
- Dewey-Stassen Debate, 27 (Box 8)
  #199 -- 16" album -- 2 copies
- Samuel Gompers, Man of Labor, 1 (Box 9)
  #200 -- 16" album
- Safety Case Histories, 2 (Box 9)
  #201 -- 16" albums
- Teamwork for Safety, 3 (Box 9)
  #201 -- 16" album
- The Secret of Supervision, 4 (Box 9)
- People Are All Alike, 5 (Box 9)
- Everybody's Different, 6 (Box 9)
- Teaching Safety on the Job, 7 (Box 9)
- Your Fortune's in My Hat / Together We Live, 8 (Box 9)
  #202 -- 16" album
- It's Up To You, 9 (Box 9)
  #312 -- 16" album -- 3 copies
- Labor Day, 10 (Box 9)
  #313 -- 16" album
- Reba Lewis, 11 (Box 9)
  #314 -- 16" album
- A.F. Whitney, 12 (Box 9)
  #315 -- 16" album
- Act of Living Together, 13 (Box 9)
  #316 -- 16" album -- 2 copies
- Meet the Press: 2/24/1948, 1 (Box 10)
  #319 -- 16" album
- Jacob S. Potofsky, 2 (Box 10)
  #318 -- 16" album
- Industrial and Labor Relations, 3 (Box 10)
  #317 -- 16" album -- 27 copies
- Forty Years Young! / ILGWU, 1 (Box 12)
  #385 (2 copies) -- 12" album
- Two: Two For The Union / ILGWU; President Lyndon B. Johnson; President John F. Kennedy, 2 (Box 12)
  #148 (2 copies) -- 12" album
- The Northeast Sings, 3 (Box 12)
  #149 (2 copies) -- 12" album
- Pins and Needles [25th Anniv. Ed.], 4 (Box 12)
  #166 -- 12" Album
- The Inheritance: From the Film Sound Track with Additional Narration, 5 (Box 12)
  #384 (3 copies) -- 12" album
- Remarks of David Sullivan on the Local 32E Trusteeship, 1966; 6 (Box 12)
  Made on the Labor News Conference of the Associated Press and Alan Adams of Business Week magazine. - Broadcast by WEVD on Jan. 7, 1966 -- Audio disc
- 5 VHS tapes from this box were moved to box 14 [#386(2 copies), #387, #388, #389], 1 (Box 13)
- Alice Kessler-Harris / 1st Alice Cook Lecture - 11/4/2004, 1 (Box 14)
  #406
- Lois W/Sen. Heinz on Channel 22 News - Fall 1988, 2 (Box 14)
  #395
- ILGWU Chorus - Florida & Luzerne County Court House 1988-1989, 3 (Box 14)
  #397
- ILGWU Chorus - 12/2/1990; Luzerne County Court House Wilkes-Barre, PA, 4 (Box 14)
  #399
- Children of Poverty, 5 (Box 14)
  #398
- ILGWU - Christmas Show - W-B Courthouse Dec. 3rd, 1989, 6 (Box 14)
  #403
- ILGWU - X-Mas Show Court House: 1988, 1989, 1990, 7 (Box 14)
  #402
- 1992 Convention in Miami Beach, 8 (Box 14)
  #401
- In The Shadow of the Tower - [Master], 9 (Box 14)
  #386
- In the Shadow of the Tower [Master], 10 (Box 14)
- UWUA - We Make America Work a History of Our Union: 6/25/2003, 11 (Box 14)
  #387
- COLA & CSAS - Sweatshop Workers Speak Out - Mexico, Dominican Republic, El Salvador: 2/17/2006, 12 (Box 14)
  #388
- Frontline: Dangerous Business / New York Times Television 1/9/2003, 13 (Box 14)
  #389
- Eyewitness Newsmakers, 14 (Box 14)
  #393
- Mt. Laurel - Unity House, 15 (Box 14)
  #392
- Channel 16, 6 pm, 11 pm, 16 (Box 14)
  #461
- Ch. 28: 4/24/1994, 17 (Box 14)
  #460
- Labor Meets Sen. Harris Wofford / Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, 18 (Box 14)
  #459
- Labor Meets Sen. Harris Wofford / Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, 19 (Box 14)
- UNITE for the future, 20 (Box 14)
  #458
- Rivets, Rations, and War / Dept. of History and Anthropology, Edinboro Univ. of PA, 21 (Box 14)
  #457
- ILGWU Chorus, Washington: 11/1989, 22 (Box 14)
  #400
- Joe Glazer: Labor Singer and Songwriter; Chicago Jewish Elders: May 17, 2006, 23 (Box 14)
  #405
- 1988 & 1989 ILGWU Chorus at Florida & Luzerne County Court House, 24 (Box 14)
- Leslie Fay NY Rally, NAFTA Harrisburg, 25 (Box 14)
  #396
- We do the work: Sewing our future, 26 (Box 14)
  #455
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight, 27 (Box 14)
  #454
- Leslie Fay Rally NYC, 9/22/1993, 28 (Box 14)
  #456
- Mt. Laurel Unity House, 29 (Box 14)
  #394
- Paul Robeson: Here I Stand, 30 (Box 14)
  #382
- Return Engagement to Garment City 2002, 1 (Box 15)
  #419
- Moving Images for the Future; Considerations in Preparation an d Printing of Deteriorating Film, 2 (Box 15)
  #420
- Strive: Segment 1: Employ.com TV, August 18, 2000; Segment 2: World News, September 6, 2000, 3 (Box 15)
  #422
- Strive on 60 Minutes, 4 (Box 15)
- The First 100 Daze, 1995; 5 (Box 15)
  #359
- Clara Lemlich: A Strike Leader's Diary [Le journal d'une meneuse de greve], 6 (Box 15)
  #415
- Every Member an Organizer, 7 (Box 15)
  #437
- Turn it Around: Teamster Stewards Solving Problems on the Job, 8 (Box 15)
  #438
- Turn it Around: Teamster Stewards Solving Problems on the Job, 9 (Box 15)
- Teamsters: Stronger than Ever, 10 (Box 15)
  #436
- Actions Speak Louder Than Words, 1995; 11 (Box 15)
  #434
- Generations: Recreating Our Future, 12 (Box 15)
  #429
- Work Worth Doing, Parts I & II / City of New York, Dept. of Sanitation, 13 (Box 15)
  #430
- It's Your Choice, 1996; 14 (Box 15)
  #433
- What You Say matters, 1996; 15 (Box 15)
  #435
- Dub of WMD raw footage, 16 (Box 15)
  #411
- Garment Workers Speak Out, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY Feb. 17, 2006, 17 (Box 15)
  #412
- Sweat: Taking the High Road in LA, 18 (Box 15)
  #413
- Sweat: Taking the High Road in Los Angeles / by Michelle Ashley and Ingrid Melendez, 19 (Box 15)
- FDL Sixth Annual Labor Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony, January 21, 1984, 20 (Box 15)
  #414
- The Triangle Factory Fire Scandal (Drama), 21 (Box 15)
  #416
- The Living Century "Three Miracles" (Home Video Version), 22 (Box 15)
  #418
- Union Summer, 23 (Box 15)
  #421
- The Past in Stock: International Institute of Social History, Amsterdam, 24 (Box 15)
  #381
- The Triangle Factory Fire Scandal: 146 Women Lose Their Lives in This Shocking Catastrophe / starring Stephanie Zimbalist, Tom Bosley, Tovah Feldshuh, 25 (Box 15)
- Legal Ethics, Howard University - 11/25/1996, 26 (Box 15)
  #431
- Smart Strategies: New Ways to Fight or Our Future, 1996; 27 (Box 15)
  #425
- Meeting the Challenge: Indiana Labor & Management Council, Inc., 28 (Box 15)
  #426
- There's Supposed to be a Law / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 29 (Box 15)
  #427
- Accommodating Differences: Disability Awareness Training for Leaders, 1997; 30 (Box 15)
  #428
- Role of Corporations in America, 31 (Box 15)
  #432
- Paycheck Economics / United Steelworkers of America, 32 (Box 15)
  #424
- Grievance Arbitration: Part IV-Argument, 1 (Box 16)
  #441
- Grievance Arbitration: Part III-Hearing, 2 (Box 16)
  #442
- Going International Pt. 4, 3 (Box 16)
  #443
- Going International Pt. 1, 4 (Box 16)
  #445
- Grievance Arbitration: Part I-Confrontation, 5 (Box 16)
  #446
- About Supervision, Everything to Know, 6 (Box 16)
  #447
- Erich Fromm, Part I, 7 (Box 16)
  #448
- Erich Fromm, Part II, 8 (Box 16)
  #449
- Changing Organizations: Designing for People and Purpose, 9 (Box 16)
  #451
- Company Town, 10 (Box 16)
  #450
- Corporation After Mr. Sam: Part II-Family, 11 (Box 16)
  #453
- Conformity and Independence, 12 (Box 16)
  #452
- The Living Century "Three Miracles", 1 (Box 17)
- ILGWU Chinatown Garment Factory, 2 (Box 17)
  #217
- New York: A Compelling Portrait of the Greatest and Most Complex of Cities, 3 (Box 17)
  #307C -- 5 tape collection
- Spirit Connection #6; Threads of Justice - Nov. 17/1997, 4 (Box 17)
  #276
- Like a Beautiful Child: A Bread and Roses Video / produced by Moe Foner, 5 (Box 17)
- New York: A Documentary Film / Part 5, 6 (Box 17)
  #307 E (dupl)
- PBS "Stopwatch" - Preview Tape / Show aired Nov. 7, 1999, 7 (Box 17)
  #321
- Never Done: The Working Life of Alice H. Cook, 1993 / by Marilyn Rivchin, Sandra Pollack, and Diane McPherson, 8 (Box 17)
  #288
- Never Done: The Working Life of Alice Cook, 9 (Box 17)
- This Week in History (Includes Triangle Fire), 10 (Box 17)
  #326
- Ric Burns. New York: A Documentary Film; Episode 4 The Power & the People, 1898-1918, 11 (Box 17)
  #307
- Marching On, 12 (Box 17)
  #277
- Labor Unions & Railroads: Then & Now, 1999; 13 (Box 17)
  #323
- FLOC 1997 Convention; Aug. 16, 1997, 14 (Box 17)
  #290A-C -- 3 VHS tapes
- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire: This Week in History, Episode 33, 1 (Box 18)
- Naomi Klein: Sweatshops on Fire; Andrew Ross: History Lesson, 2 (Box 18)
  #325
- In The Words of Frances Perkins - 1) Triangle Shirtwaist Fire; 2) Social Security, 3 (Box 18)
  #305
- Charles Wrege. PBS Interview, Tape #2: 4/25/1998, 4 (Box 18)
  #320 B
- Charles Wrege. PBS Interview, Tape #1: 4/25/1998, 5 (Box 18)
  #320A
- UWUA AFL-CIO, Local 1-2, Utility Workers: Spring 1995, 6 (Box 18)
- Charles Kernaghan, Cornell (COLA & CSAs) Nov. 16, 2005; plus Press Conference at Walmart, Nov. 17, 2005, 7 (Box 18)
- Labor Beat. The Teamsters: Who's Union is it? (c.2), 8 (Box 18)
  #287
- The Teamsters: Whose Union Is It?, 9 (Box 18)
- Harlan County USA, 10 (Box 18)
  #328
- UVAS, NO (No Grapes) - United Farm Workers, 11 (Box 18)
  Spanish version -- #286
- United Farm Workers of America "NO GRAPES", 12 (Box 18)
- They Were Not Silent: The Jewish Labor Movement & the Holocaust, 13 (Box 18)
  #284
- They Were Not Silent: the Jewish Labor Movement and the Holocaust, 14 (Box 18)
- Robert McKersie: Festschrift, October 30-31, 1998, 15 (Box 18)
  #283 (c.2)
- Rosie the Riveter, 17 (Box 18)
  #255
- Lives That Shaped a City: Stories From Baltimore's Past, 18 (Box 18)
  #274